there is no South Ossetia, this is what Lenin
нет никакой Южной Осетия это Ленин
invented specifically to make like
придумал специально чтобы сделать типа
North Ossetia and South Ossetia, Ossetia
Северная Осетия и Южная Осетия Осетия
was one Ossetia, Alania, this is us,
одна была Осетия Алания это мы
Vladikavkaz, and you, Khiva, this is Georgia, this is
Владикавказ А вы Хива это Грузия это
Georgia, you are
Грузия вы
Georgians. Hello, where are you
грузины Здравствуйте Здравствуйте Вы
from? Well, at the moment I am in Moscow,
откуда Ну в данный момент в Москве
and before this moment, where were you in
нахожусь А до данного момента Где
terms of before this moment, well, now, where were you in the name,
находился в плане до данного момента ну
you are Tula,
момен мде е вту находился наме ты туляк
no, if you are interested, my
нет из если ва интересу
father is an Ossetian from Vladikavkaz, and where are
н у меня отец осетин из Владикавказа А
you from?
ты откуда Из
Most likely, well, in
жно скорее всего ну вот в диалектах вот
these dialects, I don’t understand at all. That is, it
этих вообще не понима То есть ты из
turns out that you are from Georgia. No, it doesn’t work out. Well,
Грузии получается Да не не получается ну
Khiva is Georgia, it itself was not
с Хива это же Грузия само ч было не
Georgia, separately, no, no, no, wait. Look,
Грузия отдель нене не Подожди Смотри
what country am I. If I judge by your
какая страна меня Если судить по твоей
logic, it turns out that you are from Russia. Well, I
логике получается Ты из России Ну я
come from Russia. Yes, my father
родом из России Да мой отец
is like, we, you lived behind the ridge. You have
типа мы вы за хребтом жили Вы для нас
never been to us. Like, damn, ours. You have
никогда не были типа блин наши вы в
always lived in Georgia.
Грузии жили всегда
Well, not always. Don’t call yourself an
отрад Ну не всегда уж ты не называй себя
Ossetian. Ossetians are Vladikavkaz.
осетина осетины - это Владикавказ
Tskhinvali.  - These are not Ossetians, these are some kind of I don't
Цхинвал - Это не осети это короче
know, damn, who are
какие-то не знаю блин вы кто
you there? You came here on time. In short, damn,
там вы пона приезжали короче блин вот
this is
это
in Listen, my friend, right now
в Послушай друг мо как раз таки сейчас
Vladikavkaz And the Ruselians, so to speak, are the
Владикавказ А русел так сказать там
majority there Yes, many, many children, not to mention
большинство Да много многие дети не то
many More likely, 80% will tell you to
что многие Скорее 80% тебе скажут
speak Ossetian That's right Because,
на осетинском говорить Правильно Потому
well, the Ossetian language is what only
что ну осетинский язык что там только
this Kosta Khetagurov wrote and that's all when
этот Коста хетагуров писал и всё когда
Well, what difference does it make who wrote Why in
Ну какая разница кто писал Почему в
South Ossetia in Svali everyone can
Южной Осетии в свали все умеют на
speak Ossetian and in the North
осетинском разговаривать а в а Север
because there you had villages,
потому что там у вас там у вас деревни
only auls, and that's all Vladikavkaz, at least
только аулы были и всё Владикавказ хоть
Vladikavkaz We, at least North Ossetians, we were
Владикавказ Мы хоть северные осетины мы
developed, yes And who are you there, size
развитые были да А вы кто у вас там разм
Wait, we had a caste
Вот подожди у нас у у нас был кастах
Iguro, he made us And who are you Who
игуро он сделал нам А вы кто Вы кто кто
can you write at least one
можешь писателя хоть одного
South Ossetian writer
южноосетинский
[music]
[музыка]
obviously not like a child We are North Ossetians,
явно ня как ребёнок мы северные осетины
we are Alans, descendants of the Scythians And you for that On the
мы аланы потомки скифов А вы за за то За
other side of the ridge you are some kind of I don't know
Том стороной хребта вы какие-то не знаю
You
Вы
[music]
[музыка]
Ossetian not you some harm bring
осетинец не ты какой-то вред несёшь
conditionally blood we all in most
условно кровь у нас у всех в большинстве
cases we we are not related to you We are not
случаев мы мы с вами не родня Мы с вами
related to you We are specifically we we are
не родня Мы с вами конкретно мы мы
descendants we we Vladikavkaz we are descendants You do
потомки мы мы Влади Кавказ мы потомки Ты
n't even know You don't even know You don't even
даже не знаешь Ты даже не знаешь Ты даже
know irony you or di gorits and you
не знаешь ирони ты или ди гориц а ты
say there then I say yes Well so
говоришь там пото я говорю да Ну так
what's the difference My knowledge here I am this My
какая разница Мои познания вот я это Мои
knowledge what do you have to do with it I understand yes what's the matter
познания причём ты я понимаю да что в
Why are you Prima is called to our
этом такое Зачем ты Прима зывается к
Ossetian people of the call What are you
осетинскому народу нашему призыва Что ты
talking about my friend well by You look you've been talking about it for
несёшь друг мой ну по Ты смотри ты пред
30 years you've been
лет 30 ты
sitting arguing about who is from whom not
сидишь споришь о том кто оти на кто не
ova Georgians you Georgians this is the
ова грузины вы Грузины это само
chab itself This is there is no South Ossetia this was
чаб Вот это нет никакой Южной Осетии это
invented by Lenin specifically to make
Ленин придумал специально чтобы сделать
like North Ossetia and South Ossetia
типа Северная Осетия и Южная Осетия
Ossetia was one Ossetia Alania - this is us
Осетия одна была Осетия Алания - это мы
Vladikavkaz And you Khiva this is Georgia this is Georgia
Владикавказ А вы Хива это Грузия это
you Georgians you Georgians you just
Грузия вы грузины вы грузины вас просто
say
это говорю
this he in  grief he was from Sab
этон он в горе он был родом из Саб у
his grandmother was from Khiva Yes that's why he
него бабушка из Хива была Да он поэтому
came up with it to make a kind of South
и придумал чтобы сделать типа Южную
Ossetia so that a prize to us North
Осетию чтобы приза к нам северным
Ossetians real
осетинам настоящим
ot here he is Stalin No that's nonsense steel
оти тут он Сталине Нет это бред стали
wait Stalin I'll come under tsarist Russia there was
подожди Сталин приду при царской России
no South
не было никакой Южной
Ossetia under tsarist Russia there was
Осетии при царской России было
this Stalin and Lenin came up with and then
это Сталин с Лениным придумали да потом
South Ossetia Show me on the maps before
Южная Осетия Покажи мне на картах до
1917 Yes under Tsar Nicholas Yes so that there was
1917 года Да при царе Николая Да чтобы
South Ossetia there was no such thing
было Южная Осетия не было такого даже
at all show Ossetia was one
вообще покажи Осетия была одна
cent Lenin adj Lenin and Stalin Stalin
цент Ленин прил Ленин и Сталин Сталин
wanted a prize to the Ossetians and that's why he
захотел приза к осетинам и поэтому
came up with South Ossetia so that she would have a
придумал Южную Осетию чтобы у не бабка
much bigger grandmother Who would help
Была намного большем кто помогать будет
so to speak to herself That's how it was hop
так сказать к себе Вот так вот хоп
captured and On what year Georgia
захватила и На како в каком году Грузия
captured you In what year was Tskhinvali captured
захватила В каком году Цхинвал захвачен
in Georgia it has been Georgian from time immemorial
был в Грузией он из покон веков был
captured We also
грузинской те захвачен Мы тоже
voluntarily joined it when
добровольно вступили в его состав когда
when tell me now I'll tell you And tell me Yes I
когда скажи сейчас скажу А скажи Да я
don't know Look and  from time immemorial Yes, the
знать не зна Смотри и спокон веков Да
territory itself, the chab, the territory, it was
территория сама чаб территория это была
Georgia There was never any South
Грузия Никогда там не был никакой Южной
Ossetia there It was invented by Lenin with Stalin,
Осетии это придумал Ленин со сталином
then itself
потом сама
[music]
[музыка]
chab is inadequate really like a child Come on, come on,
чаб неадекват реально как ребнок давай
come on,
давай давай
find laziness you Stalin because Stalin
найди лень вас Сталин потому что Сталин
Yes, he himself was from the mountains He had a grandmother
Да он сам из гори у него Бабушка была
In short, from praise with his grandfather and he wanted a prize
Короче из хвала с дедом и он хотел приза
to us The great people Alano invented
к нам Великому народу алано придумал
[music]
[музыка]
u find when when Georgia captured
у знайти когда когда Грузия захватила
like South Ossetia there was never such a thing
типа Южную Осетию не было такого никогда
at all Stalin invented Stalin
вообще это Сталин придумал Сталин
invented with Lenin Ossetia come on like that see
придумал с Лени жно Осетию давай так см
everything was captured
все захватили
firstly already simply attributed to this
во-первых уже просто приписали к этому
not like that was Georgia before the
не как вот была Грузия до
USSR before the USSR You were in Georgia, but before the
СССР до сссра Вы же были в Грузии да до
USSR I don’t know, I don’t know, so Take
сссра знать не знаю се так Возьми
a look Now in Wikipedia there is Internet you can
посмотри Сейчас в Википедии Интернет
find out everything you want you can
есть можно узнать всё что хочешь можно
find out you can even ask gpt Come on
узнать можно ча gpt спросить даже
never I say you have always been
Давай никогда говорю вы всегда были
part of Georgia it was Stalin who took and
часть Грузии это Сталин сле взяли и
invented South Ossetia to call us
придумали Южную Осетию чтобы нас назвать
not Alans Ossetians  And to call us North
не аланы осетины А нас назвать Северо
Ossetians
осетины
some Come on look when Georgia
какими-то Давай ищи когда вас Грузия
captured you did not capture you were always part of
захватила не зах вы всегда были частью
Georgia this Stalin Dzhugashvili took
Грузии этот Сталин Джугашвили взял
invented
придумал
specially Caste hi agulov our
специально Каста хи агулов наш
Ossetian writer was in Vladikavkaz
осетинский писатель во Владикавказе был
yes And you If you were yes you would have your
да А у вас Если бы вы были да у вас были
own writers scientists no one Yes in
бы свои писатели учёные никого не Да
any case there is Why Netto Well then
по-любому есть Почему Нетто Ну так
look when Georgia captured you She
посмотри когда захватила Грузия вас Она
was from the dead Yes this territory is not
из покойников была Да эта территория не
so fast
так быстро
[music] is
[музыка]
located since the time of Queen Tamara
находится ещё со времён Царицы Тамары
was also there everything was
было тоже там всё было
[music]
[музыка]
WTO gorakli would and everything was there Sab part of
ВТО го ракли бы и всё там был Саб часть
Georgia
Грузии
was Abkhazia aja greli everything was all Georgia now
была абхази ажа грели всё было всё
other things That's what I have Uncle
грузи сечас прочего Вот это у меня Дядя
is in Vladikavkaz says now a
есть во Владикавказе говорит сейчас
lot of these from Tskhinvali are climbing through the
очень много этих из цхинвала лезут через
mountain and saying We too We are also Ossetians
горе и говорят Мы тоже Мы тоже осетины
Let's live in Vladikavkaz there have come
Давайте во Владикавказе жить понаехало
a
их очень
lot of them friend just now in Vla
много друг как раз-таки сейчас во Вла
Hey don't hang out brother don't hang out come on
Эй не Зависай брат не Зависай давай
find Wikipedia when did Georgia capture you
найди Википедия когда ж вас захватила
envy
завист
Brother develop snit maybe or maybe not who
Братишка разви снит может а может и нет
knows
кто его знает
everything is like
всё
I played City for a hundred and
походу как я отыграла Сити на соточку и
100 well really Georgia never
100 ну реально Грузия никогда не
captured the region itself chab Yes which
захватывала регион сама чаб Да которую
Russians call there South it has always
русски называют там Южная это всегда
been the territory of Georgia since time immemorial Yes
была территория Грузии спокон веков Да
in different times they moved there well
во времена разные там переселялись ну
these like them Ossetians from that side of the
эти как они осетины из той стороны
ridge settled a little this territory
хребта заселяли немножко эту территорию
then they settled there back then and then they
потом там пристали ещё тогда и потом они
took and said with the support of Russian
взяли и сказали при поддержке русских
troops Yes what is this like like it will be in short
войск Да что это типа типа будет короче
now a new
теперь новое
state all this and since time immemorial when
государство всё это и покон веков когда
he can't say when they captured
он не может сказать когда захватили
Because if we look Yes and
Потому что если мы посмотрим Да и
censuses Yes Georgians lived Georgians lived that's
переписи Да грузины жили грузины жили
all signature on my Telegram right
вот и всё пидпись на мий Telegram прямо
now axis VN
зараз ось ВН
apok this is very and very important YouTube is busy with
апок це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube заня
us through scarg ORV in your ban and very
нас через скарг ОРВ в твый бан и дуже
many videos are not shown to people at times are not
багато видео не показуе людям вчасно не
shown information about streams  so
показуе информация про стримы тому для
that we Mali operational link
того щоб мы Мали оперативный звязок
is written right now and Popik there in
пишиться прямо зараз а Попик там в
telegram will okrim video also interesting and
телеграми окрим видео ще теж цикава и
useful information and we will oblige you to
корисна информация и мы повинни з вами
keep constant operational link
тримати постийний оперативный звязок
independently in order to show you about this
незалежно в того чи покаже вам про це
YouTube Glory to Ukraine
YouTube Слава украини
write and
пиши а